[birds chirping]
[Taiki] Mom, where's my towel?
[Yukiko] I left it out for you.
Found it.
Of course you did.
You're right, sorry.
[gasps]
TAIKI - CHINATSU
PREFECTURAL QUALIFIERS
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
EPISODE 7
CAN I HAVE ONE?
[grunts]
- And it's Haryu for the win again!
- [grunts]
I demand a rematch!
No, thanks, dude.
[Taiki groans] Just one more, come on.
[Haryu] I mean, if you like losing.
If you get used to losing to me,
you'll probably lose to me
at the tournament, too.
Maybe that's your own self-doubt talking.
You know, since you just can't seem
- to win a match against Hyodo?
- [grunts]
[Nishida] Yeah,
and after the last tournament,
you got third in the prefecture,
and he took it all at nationals!
[in a scary voice] What was that?
Okay, let's rally.
It's about that time.
[Haryu grunts softly]
Anyway, I've got a laundry list of things
I wanna work on,
so you're on your own for practice.
[exclaims softly]
We may be doubles partners,
but we're opponents in singles.
[gasps]
You're right.
From now on,
I aim all my smashes at your crotch.
What?!
[Nagisa] I thought
we were gonna make that pass.
- [Haryu] Oh.
- Huh?
Hey, good hustle.
Yeah, good hustle.
Same to you.
Practices been exhausting lately?
[Nagisa sighs]
We have a tournament coming up.
Plus it's not just about us,
we wanna make sure
our upperclassmen get to nationals.
Whoa.
That's big of you.
[Taiki] I bet this guy's never had
a thought like that in his life.
When do the girls' qualifiers start?
[Taiki] Next Saturday.
[Nagisa] Next Saturday.
What about badminton?
Yours are on the 18th, right?
Hang on, how did you know that?
[Chinatsu] It was
in the school's newsletter.
[Nagisa] I didn't know anyone read those.
[Chinatsu] They're interesting.
The principal writes
satirical poems sometimes.
[Nagisa laughs]
That's a segment in the newsletter?
[Taiki] I wonder if Chinatsu...
is keeping an eye...
on when my tournament is, too.
SHOPPING DISTRICT
[Taiki] Ten more days till qualifiers.
Like Haryu said, I'm on my own
to fine tune everything I can
between now and then.
[groans]
Why didn't I start working
on my backhand drive sooner?
LAST-MINUTE REGRETS
[gasps]
Chinatsu.
She's carrying a lot of stuff.
Should I help her?
I'll help you!
Oh, really? Are you sure?
But...
What if someone were to see us?
[groans]
Think she's a high schooler?
- Yeah she's really cute.
- [Taiki exclaims]
Let me help carry those.
Wait, Taiki?
No, don't worry,
it's nothing I can't handle.
Plus you gotta be exhausted
from practice, too.
And anyway, you said walking home
with a girl would be uncomfortable right?
Well, I...
All right, time for take two.
Oh, aren't you Chinatsu
from the basketball team?
What are the odds, running into you here?
Do you live around here, perchance?
I live in a neighborhood
not far from here!
Looks like you could use some help.
I'll carry them.
Strength training.
Onward!
SPECIAL TECHNIQUE:
CHANCE MEETING ON THE WAY HOME
[chuckles] What are you doing?
[Chinatsu] So you live this way, too, huh?
[Taiki] I know, right? What a kawinkidink?
[Chinatsu] What a kawinkidink.
[Taiki] Fun fact,
I live in a two-story house.
Hey, I do, too.
And there's a chiropractor nearby.
I know where that is.
What's crazy is that I've only been living
at my current place since March.
And so how has it been living there?
Oh, it's been so great!
Everyone has been really sweet and kind.
The whole family
has been incredibly welcoming.
Sweet and kind?
You left a tissue in your pocket again.
Get some strength training in
and gimme a massage, would ya?
Thanks to all of them, I can keep pursuing
my dream that I almost gave up on.
[pleasant music playing]
I'm glad I moved into that house.
Chinatsu.
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
- Yes! I win.
- [groans]
I know you're super tired and everything,
but can you come with me for a sec?
- Huh?
- It's around the corner.
OYASU SHRINE
[Taiki] For years, I've visited here
the day before I have something big.
[Chinatsu] Wow, a shrine?
PRAYER FOR VICTORY
Let's go up and pray for victory.
I never knew there was a shrine here.
And in the summer,
it's a great place to catch beetles.
Bugs... scare me.
[Taiki] Chinatsu decided to live
in another person's house
just so she could pursue
her dream of going to nationals.
I have no ulterior motive.
I just want this for her as a peer.
Please... please... I pray for both
Chinatsu and I to make it to nationals.
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
Set up a net in the back court, too.
[boy] Oh. Are you sure?
What about the other clubs?
Don't worry, it's fine.
[Taiki] Oh. Right.
The basketball team's tournament
starts today.
[girl] You got it!
[all cheering]
[spectators] Eimei!
Eimei!
Eimei! Eimei!
Natsu!
[motivational music playing]
[whistle blows]
[referee] 78 to 54.
Eimei High School takes it!
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
[crying]
Nice job, Chinatsu!
Tickle, tickle, tickle...
Quit it, Nagisa. I am super sweaty.
Oh, no, but it's a victory tickle!
Nagi, don't get carried away.
The qualifiers only just started.
Ah, just lemme do my thing.
Why don't I tickle you, too?
I mean, if we're gonna get hyped,
we might as well take advantage
and go all out, right?
Well, every team has a goofball,
and I'm glad ours is you.
- Ah, well.
- [whistle blows]
- [all cheering]
- Looks like they won their game, too.
[Gomi] Guess we'll be facing
Kagohara Academy
in the finals again, huh?
We gotta take our revenge after last year.
Chinatsu.
Hello, you're zoned out.
I just really wanna win.
[chuckles] So show it on your face,
then, 'cause that's not it.
[Chinatsu] Show... what on my face?
[coach] We'll be heading back
to school shortly.
Meet by the bus in ten, yes?
[girls] Yes!
- Let's hit the bathroom.
- Mm.
And when we had that shot,
it had to be a three or bust, so then...
Ah...
KAGOHARA ACADEMY
[Nagisa] It's Kagohara...
[Kagohara player]
Is this the match that Eimei just played?
So then, number ten is gonna be Kano.
There's nothing special about her.
I got the impression she's no better
since the last practice match.
As long as I stay on her,
she won't be a problem.
It's honestly pretty disappointing.
- Uh...
- Nagisa.
Let's go.
Uh, but...
It's totally normal Kagohara would be
researching their potential opponents,
and the conclusions they draw from that
are really none of our business.
I've seen you watch the pro league,
and you seem comfortable
saying whatever you want.
[groans]
Come on.
[sighs]
LET'S GO TO NATIONALS
BADMINTON TEAM - TENNIS TEAM
[grunts]
- 21 to 14 and 21 to 13. Haryu wins.
- [panting]
What a bummer, dude.
I'm undefeated with 13 wins this month.
Thanks for the warm-up.
[Taiki] Man,
if I could beat him just once,
before the tournament starts.
I need to focus on my footwork.
And how dare he call me a "warm-up"?
- [Kikuchi] We're starting right away.
- [girls] Yes!
[Taiki] Girls' basketball is back.
Their game was earlier,
so I guess they're back to practice.
I guess you're right.
They won, didn't they?
Uh-huh, that's what the girls said.
You'd think that they would look
more excited about it.
Then again, they can't really relax
until nationals are over.
[Nagisa] If I were Chinatsu,
I'd be furious.
[Taiki] Her teammates.
To think they'd say she's nothing special,
or hasn't gotten better,
from just watching one clip?
Well, you can't go complaining
about every little comment you hear.
Yeah, I know that, but...
I think about her living situation.
We all know about it.
She's living with a relative
so that she could stay on the team,
and keep playing.
Do you know what it takes to do that?
[girl] For sure.
But Nagisa...
I mean, I absolutely hear you.
They're not gonna know
about any of that stuff,
and it has nothing to do
with what happens on the court.
But the fact is, I do know who she is
and what she's dealing with.
I can't help being pissed off.
So that's why she looked...
[gloomy music playing]
Even Chinatsu
has to face her fair share of criticism.
But I think she's perfect.
[exclaims]
I don't want them to know we're here.
What are you doing?
Why not tell me
that you were standing there?
I was spying on your spying, I guess?
[Taiki exclaims softly]
Another adorable expression.
Yeah. I have awesome teammates.
Come on, we have more windows to open.
Yeah, yeah.
I envy you.
[Chinatsu] It's funny, Nagisa is acting
like it was her they were judging.
Don't let that bother you.
No matter what the other teams
might say about you,
your team knows you work hard.
And I know how much work you put in.
- So don't let it--
- Nope. I let it bother me.
Wha...
[Chinatsu] I let it bother me,
and then I take them down.
If I play well and lead my team
to beat Kagohara,
then they'll never talk about me
like that again.
[gasps softly]
[Taiki] Wow, she's hardcore,
the "rage in silence" type.
[Chinatsu] The fact is,
that's how Kagohara felt
after watching me play,
so all I can do next time is...
show them they made
the wrong call about me.
[gasps]
[uplifting music playing]
[Taiki] Man, she's cool.
Chinatsu and Hina, they're both so cool.
They both have their own way
of going after wins.
[coach] Semifinals tomorrow, people.
You can bet it'll be
more intense than today.
2 WINS TO NATIONALS
- Keep your heads in the game!
- Yes, sir!
[shuttlecock thuds]
[all] Wow!
It can't be.
I can't believe this.
[panting]
[boy] Taiki just...
[boy 2] Won a match against Haryu.
[umpire] Second game, love all, play!
[Taiki] The worst part about facing Haryu,
is that he aims all his shots
where I least expect them.
[grunts]
[Taiki] When I think he'll drop
the shuttle near the net,
the second I shift my weight
to move there,
he sends it to my backcourt.
And his form never changes,
so I don't know where his shots
will go till the last moment.
Which means,
I need to wait patiently before I move.
Watch his racket closely.
[grunts]
[thrilling music playing]
Yes, I returned it!
Now to get back to center.
[grunts]
[exclaims]
Almost a close one.
I let my guard down.
Until recently, you wouldn't
have been able to return that. [laughs]
It's a good thing I figured that out
before the tournament.
[shuttlecock thudding]
[grunts]
Haryu completely flipped a switch
in the middle of the game.
Yeah, there aren't many guys
who have a shot at competing with him.
[boy 1] Taiki's gotten a lot better.
It's obvious his speed has improved.
All that practice paid off.
[Taiki grunts]
[boy 2] Seeing this, it makes me feel like
anything could happen in the tournament.
- [grunts]
- [whistle blows]
Right, then, everyone.
It's time to head up.
What? But things are getting good!
[Coach Yuasa] I won't hear the end of it
if I let you stay.
Besides, if you keep at it,
you'll tire yourselves out
before the tournament.
You don't wanna be
out of juice on the last day.
[Haryu] But, Coach!
You two can just save it for the finals.
Although, I don't know
when you'll face each other.
[exclaims]
[Haryu] There you have it.
We'll have our rematch another day.
And so, until then, don't lose.
[exclaims softly]
Right!
All righty, let's get this cleaned up!
- On it.
- Yes!
[Taiki] Was I
holding my own against Haryu?
I can score more points on him
than I used to.
If I'm in good shape,
I just might be able to defeat him.
Maybe take down Sajikawa,
and then make nationals.
Hey, Taiki.
I've been wondering something for a while.
Will you confess to her
if you get to nationals?
What?
CONFESS
I like you!
[Chinatsu exclaims]
MY FEELINGS
FOR
[Chinatsu] I feel closer to you already.
HER
I wanna spend more time with you.
[church bells dinging]
[exclaims in excitement]
[Kyo] You're jumping way ahead, dude.
Looks like you're
more than ready to tell her.
Well, actually,
that isn't the case at all.
Of course I want to tell her
how I feel, but...
I don't know, because what if she...
What if I get rejected, and then she...
doesn't feel comfortable
living at my house anymore?
They say it's better to regret something
you've done than something you haven't.
But I don't want to ignore
what she may be feeling,
and push my feelings on her.
Oh.
- You're all grown up, huh?
- Oh! Shut up!
- [Nishida] Taiki! Kyo!
- [Kyo] Hm?
Wazzaaaa!
- What's up?
- My dude, Yamamoto--
It's Mr. Yamamoto.
He said he's gonna treat us
since we have a tournament coming up.
Up to 500 yen a person.
That was only meant for you two!
[Kyo and Taiki] Why thank you!
Hey!
1,000 YEN
Mr. Yamamoto's cool.
You would never catch Coach Yuasa
doing something nice like that.
I wonder what we should buy.
RESORT - TOP 10 BEACHES TO GO TO
LET'S GO TO THE BEACH!
I would love to go
to the beach with Chinatsu.
Isn't that just code for
"I wanna see her in a bikini?"
Hey, Taiki.
I wasn't trying to start up
that conversation again!
I mean, there are a lot of places
I want to go with her, just the two of us.
But I gotta ask her out myself.
If I make it to nationals,
I feel like I've earned
the right to do that.
- So...
- Hm.
[Niina] The quiz had a question
on something you didn't even teach us.
[Yamamoto] Had you used the workbook
I gave you at the start of the year,
you would've answered it quite easily.
[Niina] What, like ages ago?
[whimpers]
Oops, forgot something.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[Hina] You're eating something tasty.
[Taiki] Hey! That's my fried chicken!
[Hina] Mmm.
Mr. Yamamoto paid, right?
And you're watching calories, right?
It's a good source of protein!
Deep fried protein.
Boy, are they comfortable with each other.
You aren't kidding.
Their youth is blinding me.
- [Hina] What?
- [Taiki groans]
This is fried chicken we're talking about!
[Hina] Okay, I get it, sheesh.
On the last day,
I'll bring something nice for you.
So you better stay in it till then!
I'll make you the world-renowned
Hina Bento Box Special!
[Taiki] After that conversation,
I feel awkward looking her in the eye.
[Nagisa] So we get spending money or what?
- And that's my cue!
- We're athletes, you know!
Hey! Wait!
Aren't you going to ask him
to treat you to something, Chinatsu?
He said he couldn't afford
to treat any more students, so...
can I have one?
[exclaims softly]
- Of course.
- [Chinatsu exclaims]
Thank you.
[Taiki] I didn't know she was a foodie.
Did you really want it that badly?
[Chinatsu] Yeah.
Seeing Hina ...
it made me jealous.
Huh?
Thanks for sharing.
Now I can really give my all
to my next game!
[Nagisa] Chinatsu!
Coming!
[Taiki] She meant she was jealous
about the fried chicken, right?
Or maybe...
[closing theme song playing]